Guide to the Ian P. Watt Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1990-131
  - Orwell: xeroxes (Box 32)
  - Otranto (Box 32)
  - R (Box 32)
  - James Olney (Box 32)
  - Olson, D. (Box 32)
  - O'Meally (Box 32)
  - Orgel (Box 32)
  - Otero Class (Box 32)
  - George Otte (Box 33)
  - Owen (Box 33)
  - Oxenhorn, Harvey (Box 33)
  - Packer, Barbara (Box 33)
  - Norman Page (Box 33)
  - Pagnim (Box 33)
  - PAPC:
    - 1980 Program (Box 33)
    - 1980 Rejects (Box 33)
    - Current (Box 33)
    - Newsletter (Box 33)
    - Susan Bowers (Box 33)
    - Wm. Frost (Box 33)
    - Michael Holzman (Box 33)
    - Ron Imhoff (Box 33)
    - George Otte (Box 33)
    - Stephen F. Wolfe (Box 33)
    - 1978 (Box 33)
  - Padilla (Box 33)
  - Pagnini, Marcello (Box 33)
  - Paermo Itineraries, Expenses (Box 33)
  - Paris, Arthur '79 (Box 33)
  - Catherine Parke (Box 33)
  - Parnassus Plays (Box 33)
  - Parsons (Box 33)
  - Paterson (Box 33)
  - Pasternak (Box 33)
  - Pauling, Linus (Box 33)
  - Paz, Francis 77-A (Box 33)
  - Otis Pease (Box 34)
  - Lowry PEI (Box 34)
  - Pelligin (Box 34)
  - Penn State (Box 34)
  - Perez, Vincent (Box 34)
  - Pessimism (Box 34)
  - John Peters (Box 34)
  - Picaresque (Box 34)
  - Pickett, Todd (Box 34)
  - Pillrek, Joan E. '79 (Box 34)
  - PIV (Box 34)
  - Dana Polan (Box 34)
  - Poland Award and Correspondence (Box 34)
  - Polhemus (Box 34)
  - Pope (Box 34)
  - Popular Culture (Box 34)
  - Portland Trip (Box 34)
  - Post, Gaines (Box 34)
  - Post Modernist (Box 34)
  - Pound, Ezra (Box 34)
  - Powers (Box 34)
  - Mary Pratt (Box 34)
  - Prentice-Hall, Royalties (Box 34)
  - Prince, Michael (Box 34)
  - Princeton (Box 34)
  - Madeleine Pritchard (Box 34)
  - Prostro, Jack (Box 34)
  - Psychology (Box 34)
  - Purdue University Press - MS. (Box 34)
  - Purdy, Dwight H. (See Minnesota, Univ. of) (Box 34)
  - Purl, Douglas '77-A (Box 34)
  - Q (Box 34)
  - Queens Visit 1983 (Box 34)
  - R #2: 1970 - (Box 35)
  - R #1: -1969 (Box 35)
  - Rabin-Wickham File (Box 35)
  - Rader, Ralph (Box 35)
  - Raleigh (Box 35)
  - Raleigh: Joyce & Memory (Box 35)
  - Raritan-Quarterly Review (Box 35)
  - Ratner, Leonard (M. Miller, The Portable Stanford) (Box 35)
  - Raval, Suresh (Box 35)
  - Gordon Ray (Box 35)
  - Reader Criticism (Box 35)
  - Reading (Box 35)
  - Cornell Paper, Novel Criticism (Box 35)
  - A.L. Austin on Realism (Box 35)
  - Cornell Talk Drafts (Box 35)
  - Cornell Talk on Novel (Box 36)
  - Realism Paper (Box 36)
  - The Novel and Realism: Notes used for Notes (Box 36)
  - Tuscaloosa Realism Talk Spares (Box 36)
  - Tuscaloosa Talk Notes Etc (Box 36)
  - Graff Articles (Box 36)
  - Houston Paper on Novel, Used Notes (Box 36)
  - Rebholz (Box 36)
  - Recommendations - 1964 on, A-F (Box 36)
  - Recommendations - 1964 on, G-P (Box 36)
  - Recommendations - 1964 on, Q-Z (Box 36)
  - Letters of Recommendation A-L (Box 36)
  - Letters of Recommendation M-Z (Box 36)
  - Reconstruction (Box 36)
  - Remak (Box 36)
  - Rendall, Thomas (Box 36)
  - Rehm, Rush (Box 37)
  - Reports for Foundations (Box 37)
  - Michael B. Reuben (Box 37)
  - Gale-Reprints (Box 37)
  - Reviews by Watt: Offprints (Box 37)
  - Reviews-Johnson (Box 37)
  - Joseph Andrews Review (Box 37)
  - Macdonald (Box 37)
  - Mayo Review (Box 37)
  - In Newspapers (Box 37)
  - Parish Article (Box 37)
  - Richardson Review (Box 37)
  - Scott Review (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller Foundation: (Commission on the Humanities) (Box 37)
  - Rockefeller Fellowship - 1985/6 (Box 37)
  - Robatyn (Box 37)
  - Roberts, Dave (Box 37)
  - Roberts, David '79 (Box 37)
  - Robinson, B.L. '79 (Box 37)
  - Yosal Rogat (Box 37)
  - F Rogers (Box 37)
  - Rohatyn on Orwell (Box 37)
  - Rorke (Box 37)
  - Michelle Rosaldo (Box 37)
  - Rosenthal (Box 38)
  - Rosmarin (Box 38)
  - Rosovsky, Henry (Dean, Art & Sciences, Harvard) (Box 38)
  - Rousseau (Box 38)
  - Rousseau Chronology (Box 38)
  - Rousseau, George S. (Box 38)
  - Ruiz, Edward - David '75 (Box 38)
  - Ruotolo (Box 38)
  - S #2 - 1970 on (Box 38)
  - S #1 (Thru 1969) (Box 38)
  - Ian Watt (Box 38)
  - Sartre (Box 38)
  - Saskatoon (Box 38)
  - Mark Sauin (Box 38)
  - Schacht, Paul (Box 38)
  - Schleiss (Box 38)
  - Hilary Schor (Box 39)
  - School Official 1983 Conference (Box 39)
  - Mark Schorer (Box 39)
  - Schorer Talk (Box 39)
  - Schwendiger Conrad Talk (Box 39)
  - Schwarz, Daniel R. (Box 39)
  - S.E.L. (Box 39)
  - Search/Selection Procedures (EXEMPT) (Box 39)
  - Sears, Robert (Box 39)
  - Charles Seavey (Box 39)
  - Sebeok, Thomas (Box 39)
  - Marie Seed (Box 39)
  - Laura Seitel (Box 39)
  - Semel Jay '75 (Box 39)
  - Serres, Michael (Box 39)
  - Sequoia Travel (Box 39)
  - Shaftesbury (Box 39)
  - Shanahan (Box 39)
  - Alison Shanks (Box 39)
  - Shapiro, Vivan '75 (Box 39)
  - Shasky Florian (Box 39)
  - Shea, Daniel (Box 39)
  - Shereikis, Richard '77 (Box 39)
  - George Simson (Box 39)
  - Sylvia Sieferman (Box 39)
  - Simmel (Box 39)
  - David Simpson (Box 39)
  - Simpson, Louis (Box 39)
  - Adam Smith (Box 39)
  - David Smith (Box 39)
  - Smith, Horatio E. (Box 39)
  - Society of Fellows (Box 39)
  - Louise Solomon (Box 39)
  - Sorokin, Boris '77 (Box 39)
  - Carol Spies (Box 40)
  - Spender (Box 40)
  - Spilka (Box 40)
  - Spitz, Lew (Box 40)
  - John Stape (Box 40)
  - Sondra Stang (Box 40)
  - SHC Early Letters (Box 40)
  - Watt Lunch '83 June 4th Also '84 (Box 40)
  - SHC Expenses, My Research (Box 40)
  - SHC - Current (Box 40)
  - Stanford U. (Box 40)
  - Stegner, Wally (Box 40)
  - Steiner, George (Box 40)
  - Steinlight, Stephen '77 (Box 40)
  - Stendhal (Box 40)
  - Stephenson, Frank (Box 40)
  - Stepto (Box 40)
  - Peter Stern (Box 40)
  - Stockdale, James B. (Box 40)
  - Stoehr (Box 40)
  - Stone, Will (Box 40)
  - Graham Stoney (Box 40)
  - Storhoff, Gary '79 (Box 40)
  - Straulman (Box 40)
  - Strehle (Box 40)
  - Structuralism (Box 40)
  - Jerzy Strzetelski (Box 40)
  - Studies in Short Fiction (Box 40)
  - Style (Box 40)
  - Alvin Sullivan (Box 40)
  - Italo Suevo (Box 40)
  - Swidler, Ann (Box 40)
  - Swift (Box 40)
  - T (Box 40)
  - (Jane Austen) Washington U. 1982 (Box 41)
  - B.B.C.: Past (Box 41)
  - Cary, Joyce (Box 41)
  - Century Club Talk (Box 41)
  - Conrad Talk, Author's Coffee (Box 41)
  - English in England, Ian Watt (Box 41)
  - Talk - 396-1978 "Eighteenth Century" (Box 41)
  - University Fellows Talk (Watt) (Box 41)
  - Keswick Talk (Box 41)
  - Library Talk 1984 (Box 41)
  - Library - Conrad (Box 41)
  - Los Angeles Talk (Box 41)
  - Los Trancos (Box 41)
  - Modern British Fiction (B) (Box 41)
  - Nineteenth Century Novel (Box 41)
  - NCTE Talk (Box 41)
  - Talk to Review Club (Box 41)
  - Roxana (Box 41)
  - S.F. School District Talk (Box 41)
  - Seminars - Manchestor Talk (Box 41)
  - HI My Sartre Talk (Box 41)
  - Sterne (Box 41)
  - Stanford in England (Box 41)
  - Tanner Tald - KWAI (Box 41)
  - Tarnawski, Wit (Box 41)
  - Tawney, R.H. (Box 41)
  - Teaching 1984-5 (Box 42)
  - Course Committees 1978-9 (Box 42)
  - Curriculum - 1978 (Box 42)
  - French Translation Exams (Box 42)
  - Space Committee 1978-9 (Box 42)
  - Star Trek (Box 42)
  - 131 - Lectures Given (Box 42)
  - Graduate Placement (Box 42)
  - SLE 1980 (Box 42)
  - Humanities, English Honors Essays - 1983 (Box 42)
  - Whiting Applications (Box 42)
  - English Dept. Grad Handouts (Box 42)
  - Departmental - Current (Box 42)
  - Western III Culture (Box 42)
  - GWWC - III Exams 1982 (Box 42)
  - GWWC - III (Box 42)
  - GWWC - III Handouts (Box 42)
  - Freshman English - Current (Box 42)
  - English 7 (Box 42)
  - English 10A - Fall '73 (Box 42)
  - 30 Used (Box 42)
  - Exams, Quizzes, Gradesheets (Box 42)
  - English 30 - Notices (Box 42)
  - Novel 30 - 130 Winter 1988 (Box 42)
  - 35 Exams Etc (Box 43)
  - English 35 Class Folder (Box 43)
  - English 35 Bibliography (Box 43)
  - English 35 1983 (Box 43)
  - Hum 63 (Chaco) (Box 43)
  - Hum 63 Past Lists and Exams (Box 43)
  - Hum 63 Handouts (Box 43)
  - Humanities 63 General Notes (Box 43)
  - English 100E Winter 1978 (Box 43)
  - English 100 - Conrad (Box 43)
  - English 100E - Conrad (Box 43)
  - 231 Fall, 1977 Organization, Class Lists, Grades, etc (Box 43)
  - Fielding (Box 43)
  - Smollett (Box 43)
  - Tristram Shanoy (Box 43)
  - Rasselas (Box 43)
  - Dostoevsky (361) (Hum 63) (Box 43)
  - Great Expectations (Box 43)
  - Thomas Mann 361 (Box 43)
  - Mann Handout (Box 44)
  - Mann Death in Venice (Box 44)
  - Forster - Handout (Box 44)
  - E.M. Forster - Xeroxes (Box 44)
  - Forestor, E.M. (Box 44)
  - Forster: Passage to India, Whitman - Handout (Box 44)
  - Gatsby (Box 44)
  - Camus (Box 44)
  - Solzhenityn (Box 44)
  - 231 - Past Lectures (Box 44)
  - Moll Flanders (Box 44)
  - Pamela (Box 44)
  - English 241 - 1974,1977 (Box 44)
  - English 241 - Fall 1969 (Box 44)
  - English 241 Current Notes (Box 44)
  - English 241 Winter 1971: Past Notes (Box 44)
  - English 241 - Exams & Assignments (Box 45)
  - 131A - 1979 (Box 45)
  - Tom Jones (Box 45)
  - English 188B Fall 1969 (Box 45)
  - English 188B Fall 1969 (Box 45)
  - 288F - Conrad (Box 45)
  - 288F - Marklist - 1978 (Box 45)
  - English 307(a): Spring 1968 (Box 45)
  - SS 301 1970 (Box 45)
  - English 192: Current (Box 45)
  - The Monk [1] (Box 45)
  - The Monk [2] (Box 45)
  - Fanny Burney (Box 45)
  - Mysteries of Udolpho (Box 45)
  - Frankenstein (231-B) Notes (Box 45)
  - Goldsmith, Vicar of Wakefield (Box 45)
  - English 193 (Box 45)
  - English 193: Winter 1966 (Box 45)
  - English 231 - Fall '77 (Box 46-47)
  - 231B - Gothic Bibliography (Box 46-47)
  - 288F - Exams (Box 46-47)
  - English 231B - Course Folder, Winter 1975 (Box 46-47)
  - 231B - 1975 Readings & Exams (Box 46-47)
  - Foster: 269 (Box 46-47)
  - 307A (Box 46-47)
  - 307C (Box 46-47)
  - Hume, etc 309(?) [303]? (Box 46-47)
  - Walpole - Otranto (Box 46-47)
  - Montesquieu (Box 46-47)
  - Deism, etc (Box 46-47)
  - Montesquieu 303 (Box 46-47)
  - Voltaire (Box 46-47)
  - Kant 303 (Box 46-47)
  - 303c Handouts (Box 46-47)
  - 303c Spring 1989 (Box 46-47)
  - Enlightenment - Library Printouts (Box 4647)
  - Rousseau - 303F (Box 46-47)
  - 303F - Diderot Notes (Box 46--47)
  - Enlightenment Course, Spring 1989 (Box 46-47)
  - Hume (Box 46-47)
  - Kant (Box 46-47)
  - 303 Progress (Box 46-47)
  - 303 Gibbon (Box 46-47)
  - Adam Smith (Box 46-47)
  - [Voltaire - Lectures] – empty (Box 46-47)
    [The dividing line between boxes 46 and 47 was lost in the creation of the listing.]
  - Boswell (Box 48)
  - Books - Current (Box 48)
  - Godwin (Box 48)
  - 18 Science (?) (18 Cents) (Box 48)
  - Enlightenment (Box 48)
  - 315 Xeroxes (Box 48)
  - Diderot (Box 48)
  - 315A - 1978 18 Cent. Novel (Box 48)
  - 315F - used notes (Box 48)
  - 315F - 1978 (Box 48)
  - English 315 - Autumn 1974 (Box 48)
  - Locke - the State 315F (Box 48)
  - 315B Enlightenment, Biblia (Box 48)
  - 314G - 1979 (Box 48)
  - 314G used Bibliography (Box 48)
  - Augustanism & Defue 315F (Box 48)
  - Used Lectures - C4 18c. Ideas (Box 48)
  - 315F Swift & Pope (Box 48)
  - 315F (Box 48)
  - Library Checking 18C Novel 315F (Box 48)
  - Stanford 340 (Box 49)
  - English 340 - Notes (Box 49)
  - English 340 - Current (Box 49)
  - English 341 (Box 49)
  - English 341 - Winter 1966 (Box 49)
  - 341A - Winter 1969 (Box 49)
  - 341A - Fall 1967, Winter 1968 (Box 49)
  - English 358A 1970 (Box 49)
  - Arnold - 361 (Box 49)
  - Baudelaire 361 (Box 49)
  - Darwin Notes (Box 49)
  - 361 1980 (Box 49)
  - Nietzsche 361 (Box 49)
  - 361 Xeroxes (Box 49)
  - English 361 - 1979 Used Notes (Box 49)
  - 361 - Organization (Box 49)
  - 361 - Paradigm (Box 49)
  - English 361 Class Records (Box 49)
  - 361 - Class Folder 1979 (Box 49)
  - 361 - Bibliography (Box 49)
  - Austen Seminar 384 (Box 49)
  - Jane Austen, Ad Hoc Seminar, Autumn 81-82, 395 (Box 49)
  - 395 - 1981 Used Handouts, Records (Box 49)
  - English 395 Austen Seminar 1982 (Box 49)
  - English 386 - 1971 (Box 49)
  - Graduate talks 1983-84 Lewalski (Box 50)
  - Graduate talk 396 (Box 50)
  - Teaching: Student Evaluations (Box 50)
  - Course bibliographies (by other teachers) (Box 50)
  - Desk Copies - Forms & Orders (Box 50)
  - SLE - 1981 (Box 50)
  - Berkeley:
    - 160 Conrad (Box 50)
    - Teaching: UBC English 427 (Box 50)
    - 44b - Notes (Box 50)
    - 46A - 1959 (Box 50)
    - Single Copies 160 Exams (Box 50)
    - Othello Lecture 100 (Box 50)
    - 100 - Spring 1957 (Box 50)
    - Teaching Notes 100 (Box 50)
    - 44B Aural & Visual (Box 50)
  - Balzac 44B (Box 50)
  - Eliot 44B (Box 50)
  - Berkeley:
    - Molieve (Box 50)
    - Milton (Box 50)
    - S160 Auden & Thomas (Box 50)
    - 151K Joyce (Box 50)
    - 160 Wells (Box 50)
    - Reading List Schedule (Box 50)
    - S160 Early Lecture (Box 50)
    - Yeats (Box 50)
    - Early 18C. Novel (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 50)
    - 203Q 1961 (Box 50)
    - 203Q Recordings of Mod. Brit. Lit. (Box 51)
    - 1962-203Q Bibl. Handouts (Box 51)
    - 1961 203Q Bibliography (Box 51)
    - English 260 Handouts (Box 51)
    - 260 - Spring '58 (Box 51)
    - Joyce - Bibliography 260 (Box 51)
    - 260 - 1960 (Box 51)
    - English 269 1958 (Box 51)
    - 269 Fall 1956 (Box 51)
    - Prose Improvement (Box 51)
  - Hawaii 1967 Conrad 685 (Box 51)
  - 775 - Conrad (Box 51)
  - Hawaii 1967: 447 (Box 51)
  - Joyce (Box 51)
  - Hawaii 469 - Current Lecture (Box 51)
  - Lucky Jim (Box 51)
  - Trollope (Box 51)
  - 469 - used (Box 51)
  - Hawaii Course Notes (Box 51)
  - Teaching Matter Hawaii-Mine (Box 51)
  - Hawaii - Correspondence Citizen's Chair (Box 51)
  - Civilization - Nice (Box 51)
  - Nature - Nice (Box 51)
  - Current - Novel Lectures (Box 51)
  - Tours - 7A (Masterpieces) (Box 52)
  - English 151 - Not Current (Box 52)
  - English 7A - Not Current (Box 52)
  - Tours - 272A Poetry Since 1945 (Box 52)
  - Tours: Administrative (Box 52)
  - Tours: 281 Nature (Box 52)
  - 281 Notes (Box 52)
  - Tours: English 151 - Novel in 19 Cent. (Box 52)
  - Alice (Box 52)
  - Camus (Box 52)
  - Williams: 361 English Comic Novel (Box 52)
  - Williams - Candide Hum. 63 (Box 52)
  - Williams Hum. 387: Problems in Criticism & Scholarship (Box 52)
  - Tennyson (Box 52)
  - Terrorism Conference (Box 52)
  - (Univ. of) Texas, at Austin (Box 52)
  - Xerox: Scott & U.S. (Texas) (Box 52)
  - Texas Arrangements (Box 52)
  - Thacher (Box 52)
  - Thacher People (Box 52)
  - Thalheimer, Fred '77 (Box 52)
  - Thalia (Box 52)
  - Thomas, Dylan (Box 52)
  - Dave Thorburn (Box 52)
  - Thortor, L.A. Complete '75 (Box 52)
  - Thorton, Robert (Box 52)
  - Tillman, Alexander (Box 53)
  - Toronto (Box 53)
  - Trollope (Box 53)
  - Tristram Shandy - Notes for Introduction (Box 53)
  - Tristram Shandy - Corrections & Additions (Box 53)
  - Trollope Conference (Box 53)
  - Tuscaloosa Arrangements (Box 53)
  - [Jenny Tseng] - not labeled up to p (Box 53)
  - -U- (Box 53)
  - University Lectures (Box 53)
  - Updike (Box 53)
  - Utah, Univ. of: Council, Normap (Box 53)
  - -V- (Box 53)
  - Vanderbilt, Kilroy (Box 53)
  - Vendler (Box 53)
  - Victoria Trip Arrangements (Box 53)
  - Victorian Studies (Box 53)
  - Villiers, de L'Isle - Adam (Box 53)
  - Vinge, Louise (Box 53)
  - Virginia, 1980 (Box 53)
  - -W- (Box 53)
  - S. Wali (Box 53)
  - War (Box 53)
  - (Housley) Warhol (Box 54)
  - Dr. L.O. Warren (Box 54)
  - U of Washington, etc. (Box 54)
  - Wasserman (Box 54)
  - Watson, George (Box 54)
  - Biographical Publications (Box 54)
  - Past Bio-bibliographies (Box 54)
  - Biographical stuff - to 1972 (Box 54)
  - Bio-bibliography - Former Versions (Box 54)
  - Bio-bibliography - Past Versions (Box 54)
  - Bio-bibliography: Materials up to '79 (Box 54)
  - MLA - Conrad (Box 54)
  - Bio-bib Materials 1983- (Box 54)
  - Watt Talks: 1983- (Box 54)
  - MT & L Handouts, etc. (Box 54)
  - University Committees - French Chair (Box 54)
  - History Search Committee (Box 54)
  - University Committees (Box 54)
  - Visits to Universities, etc. Not Current - Mine (Box 54)
  - Private letters - MTL Academic (Box 54)
  - Visits to Universities, etc. Current - Mine (Box 54)
  - Visiting Lectures offers, etc (Box 54)
  - WACAC Meeting 13 Jan 84 (Box 55)
  - [unlabeled folder - artic. about Janet Weiss (Cooper)] (Box 55)
  - Whiting (Box 55)
  - George Williams Visit (Box 55)
  - Williams Appointment - Travel (Box 55)
  - Winters, Janet (Box 55)
  - Yvor Winters (Box 55)
  - U. of Wisconsin (Box 55)
  - Wittgenstein (Box 55)
  - Winnepeg Trip (Box 55)
  - [loose stuff] (Box 55)
  - World Book Articles (Box 55)
  - George Wrangele (Box 55)
  - Andy Wright (Box 55)
  - Dickens's Humor (Box 55)
  - Cuttings (Box 55)
  - [unlabeled Folder - more cuttings] (Box 55)
  - Chapter 4 - Notes for Ch. 4 & bibliography (Box 55)
  - E.P. Ch I (Box 55)
  - E.P. Intro (Box 55)
  - Notes to add to 1st 3 Ch's (Box 55)
  - Chap. 2 - Fair Copy Addenda (Box 55)
  - Myth of the Kwai, correspondence re publishing, 1968 (Box 56)
  - Myths of the Kwai – used (drafts and a few notes) (Box 56)
  - Kwai: Observer & Life [actually contains typescript of "The Myth of the Kwai" and correspondence with Nigel Lloy of the Observer 1968; and photocopy of the article published in The Listener, 1959] (Box 56)
  - Siam Brochures and clippings (Box 56)
  - P.O.W. stuff: typescript "A Chap in Dark Glasses," manuscript notes; and typescript "Japanese – Prisoner of War Language" (Box 56)
  - Revenge of Mercy [actually contains typescript "The Ways of Guilt" with some miscellaneous notes and a clipping] (Box 56)
  - The Strangest Thing, typescript (Box 56)
  - The Gahanese Character [typescript entitled "The Japanese"] (Box 56)
  - Lazybones; or Politics in South-East Asia – final drafts with correspondence from publishers (Box 56)
  - Maves, Forward by Watt to Carl Maves book Sensuous Pessimism with correspondence, 1971-74 (Box 56)
  - Mirrors [postcard from Bernice Zelditch with image of mirror in art work 1968] (Box 56)
  - Novelist as Innovator – series on novelists from The Listener, 1965 (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous Talks, typescripts and notes, 1955-63 and undated (Box 56)
  - Monk Festschrift, Correspondence and draft of "The Comic Syntax of Tristram Shandy" 1963-64 (Box 56)
  - Nostromo – correspondence and notecards 1957 (Box 56)
  - Weiss, Ted, correspondence, 1984 (Box 56)
  - Weinstein, Bernard, correspondence, 1979-82 (Box 56)
  - Welsh, Alexander, correspondence, 1983-88 (Box 56)
  - Western Humanities Conference (Box 56)
  - Wollaeger, Mark, correspondence, 1979-89 (Box 56)
  - Women & Lit (Janet Todd, ed.), correspondence, 1981 (Box 56)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship 1975 (Box 56)
  - Wolfe, Thomas (Box 57)
  - Mary Wood (Box 57)
  - Wood, Michael (Box 57)
  - Woodmansce (Box 57)
  - Virginia Woolf 1983 (Box 57)
  - Wordsworth 361 (Box 57)
  - Wydawnictwo Morskie (Box 57)
  - Worldbook (Box 57)
  - X-Y-Z (Box 57)
  - Yale up (Box 57)
  - Yeager (Box 57)
  - Lee Yearly (Box 57)
  - Yeats (Box 57)
  - Yeazell (Box 57)
  - Young, Steve (Box 57)
  - Young, Steve - Notes on Rockefeller Report (Box 57)
  - Zemka (Box 57)
  - Zirker, Malvin (Box 57)
  - Zola (Box 57)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1994-106
  - "A" (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abrams, Billy (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abrams, M.H. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adorno, Theodor W. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annan, Noel (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Auden, W.H. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Augustan Anthology (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Austen, Jane. Prentice"Hall, Correspondence / Accounts. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jane Austen Society (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Jane Austen Society Annual Meeting"October 1981. [Ian Watt Talk] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Asch, Sue (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "B" (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Backschneider, Paula (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bard (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Beasley, Jerry C. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Berkeley. Departmental Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Berman, Russell (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bishop Notes (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bloom, Harold (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bouit (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bourdieu, Pierre (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bourdieu Conference (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bronsons (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Budget Letter other personal (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "C" (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cahill (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cambridge (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Canada Council (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Casablanca (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chatto and Windus (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - China (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Churchill, Harold (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "Clarissa"by Ian Watt (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cohn, Lowell (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Conrad Conference. University of Miami. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Conrad Decoding (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Conrad Review (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Corke, Michael (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "D" (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dennis, Nigel (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dey, Douglas B. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Disorder and Order"; Notes and Photocopies. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dupee, F. W. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "E" (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Editorial Correspondence: Journals (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Editor's Correspondence: Presses (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Editorial Correspondence: Not Presses or Magazines (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Edmonton: Correspondence about Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Encyclopedia Brittanica (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - English, Jim (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ervine, St. John (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Expectations Project (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "F" (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fan Mail (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Forcione, Alban (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ford, Boris (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Forster, E. M. Current Lectures. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Forster, E. M. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - France (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Frank Festschrift (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Frankfurt School (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - French Revolution (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Freud, Siegmund (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Fromm Institute"Austen 1990"91 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fromm Institute"Austen 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fromm Institute"Austen 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Furbank, P. N. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "G"(1) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "G"(2) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - "G"(3) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Gillon, Adam (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Girard, Rene (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Goody, Jack (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Goody, Jack: "Literacy". (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Gothic Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Gothic: Bronson Version. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gothic"Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "On Gothic Times", Notes. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Gothic Paper. 1980 Revision. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Gothic: Xeroxes. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Greene Stuff (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "H" (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Heldt, Lucia (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Helliwell, Alex (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - History (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hobday, Reuben (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hobsbawm, Eric (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hough, Graham (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Howe, Irwing (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - HuangXinqu (Frank) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Humanities and Stanford (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Humanities Center (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Humanities Center [Expenses 1980"83] (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Humanities Conference 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Humanities Institute 1983/84. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Humanities West (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - IAUPE (1) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IAUPE (2) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - IAUPE (3) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "J" (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Jackson Eli Reynolds Professor of Humanities (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Jackson Eli Reynolds Professorship [Accounts 1983/84"current] (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Jackson Eli Reynolds Professorship [Accounts] (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jackson Eli Reynolds Professorship [Research Claims] (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - James, Henry (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sociological Jargon (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Johnson (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - St. John's College (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "K" (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Kennedy, Donald. Correspondence. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Genre (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Islas, Arturo (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Kosciuszko Foundation (Box 8, Folder 3)